defenderhosting.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Virtacore

By accessing Virtacore’s website or enrolling or using any services on such website (collectively the “Services”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is part of the terms that you must agree to in connection with your use of our site and the Services. If you do not agree to any of the terms in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Services.

Virtacore reserves the right to change the provisions of this Privacy Policy from time to time at our sole discretion. You should check the Virtacore website from time to time to confirm that you continue to agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We respect your privacy and security, this Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices with respect to our website and the Services and it sets forth what personally identifiable information of yours that we may collect, how and when such information is used, how we protect such information, and who has access to the information.

### Collection of Personal Information

When you create an account and when you use or provision the Services, we will ask you to provide certain information about yourself or your organization (if you are using the Services on behalf of your organization). You may be required to provide your name, address, telephone number, payment account information (a valid credit card or debit card) and a valid email address. We may also ask for your employer name, job title and department and telephone numbers when you are using the services on behalf of an organization. We may also require that any other user that you authorize to use the services provide such information. Further, you will be required to create a password and certain security questions and answers, which may have personal information. Each time you log in to your account and use the services, you will be required to provide your username or email and password. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to use the services or access certain parts of our website.

When you use the services, you may upload user content that includes your personal information, data and content. Although we do not necessarily intend on reviewing all of such content, we do reserve the right to monitor such content to confirm it complies with applicable terms of service or similar agreements.

### Use of Personal Information

We use your personal information to help you use the Services, to bill for the Services, and to send you notices with respect to the Services.

In the process of administering our site and in providing the Services, we may maintain and track usage through Web server logs and other network tools. These tools provide such information such as the following:

  * The date of the visit
  * The time and length of the visit
  * The path taken through the Site
  * The browser being used
  * A list of files or information downloaded or viewed
  * The Internet Protocol (IP) address of the machine accessing the Site
  * Any errors encountered
  * How many servers are accessed
  * How much bandwidth is used
  * How much processing power is performed on any data or content

We do not associate sensitive data, such as race, religion, sexual orientation, ethnicity or political affiliations, with personally identifiable information. We take precautions to segregate any sensitive data a user may provide that references a user’s race, religion, sexual orientation, ethnicity or political affiliations.

We use anonymous demographic and other information to aid the technical administration of our website and the Services and to better understand how the website and the Services are functioning for our end-users.

In some instances, “cookies” or a similar technology may be used. If you do not wish to accept a cookie from our servers, you can adjust the settings on your browser accordingly.

### How We Share Your Personal Information

We will not sell, rent or lease to others telephone numbers, e-mail addresses or other personal information. We will share the personal data you provide only with our affiliates and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf to provide the Services.

### Consent

We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer or user information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. You consent to the foregoing by using the Services.

### Personal information received from the EU – Safe Harbor compliance

Virtacore complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Virtacore has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

In compliance with the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles, Virtacore commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Virtacore at:

Virtacore  
ATTN: Compliance Officer  
21355 Ridgetop Circle  
Suite 250  
Sterling, VA 20166

Virtacore has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Virtacore, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.

### Privacy related concerns

Should you have questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Policy or compliance with it, please send an e-mail to: safeharbor@virtacore.com.
